<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Homepage on Ricardo Dahis</title><link>https://rdahis.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Homepage on Ricardo Dahis</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://rdahis.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://rdahis.github.io/sections/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rdahis.github.io/sections/about/</guid><description>I am a Senior Lecturer (a.k.a. advanced assistant professor) at the Department of Economics at Monash University. My research interests lie at the intersection of Development, Politics, and Environmental Economics. I hold a Ph.D in Economics from Northwestern University. My research has been published in journals such as the Review of Economics and Statistics and the Journal of Public Economics.
I have co-founded Data Basis (Base dos Dados), a nonprofit start-up with the mission to make access to high-quality data universal in Brazil and internationally.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://rdahis.github.io/sections/advising-teaching/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rdahis.github.io/sections/advising-teaching/</guid><description>For current and prospective students, RAs, and postdocs: please read this.
Advising Hours (PUC-Rio only): Shedule here.
Office Hours (PUC-Rio only): Shedule here.
Office Hours (for those outside RJ and SP or members of under-represented groups): Shedule here.
Teaching:
ECON 2201: Grad Development Economics (materials)
ECON 2701: Grad Statistics (materials)
ECON 1341: Introdução à Economia Aplicada</description></item><item><title/><link>https://rdahis.github.io/sections/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rdahis.github.io/sections/contact/</guid><description>Email: rdahis@econ.puc-rio.br
NOTE: For Data Basis-related issues, please contact the project directly, read the documentation and FAQ, or ask the community on Discord! I may not reply to email about it (why?).
Address: PUC-Rio. Rua Marquês de São Vicente 225, 2º andar, Departamento de Economia. Rio de Janeiro, RJ - 22541-041, Brazil</description></item><item><title/><link>https://rdahis.github.io/sections/personal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rdahis.github.io/sections/personal/</guid><description>Ice Cream Map: Mapping and reviewing ice cream spots worldwide, one at a time.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://rdahis.github.io/teaching/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rdahis.github.io/teaching/</guid><description>Ricardo Dahis | Teaching Ricardo Dahis Assistant Professor, PUC-Rio
Back
Statistics, PUC-Rio Slides 1. Probability Theory 2. Transformations and Expectations 3. Distribution Families 4. Random Vectors 5. Random Sampling 6. Data Reduction 7. Point Estimation 8. Hypothesis Testing 9. Asymptotics Problem Sets PS1 PS2 PS3 PS4 PS5 PS6 Tópicos em Desenvolvimento Econômico, PUC-Rio Ementa Slides 1.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://rdahis.github.io/working-with-me/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rdahis.github.io/working-with-me/</guid><description>Ricardo Dahis | Working together Ricardo Dahis Assistant Professor, PUC-Rio
Back
Managing healthy and productive work relationships Hello world! Collaborating and advising is not easy so I try to keep the flow of information and tasks efficient. Please read below if you work with me or intend to. Principles of time management The first principle to understand is that we are mortals.</description></item></channel></rss>